### Contact

amberharris0103@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/amber-harris-548706b3 (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Healthcare

Nursing

**Patient Safety** 

### Certifications

Basic Life Support for Healthcare Providers (BLS)

Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS)

# **Amber Harris**

Nurse Clinician/Coordinator at UCSF Benioff Children's Hospital Oakland

San Francisco, California

# Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Pediatric Intensive Care and Case Management. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science in Nursing (BSN) from Kent State University.

## Experience

UCSF Benioff Children's Hospital Oakland Nurse Clinician/Coordinator June 2019 - Present (1 year 2 months) Oakland, CA

**Pediatric Cardiology** 

Kaiser Permanente

5 years 4 months

Case Management Nurse February 2019 - Present (1 year 6 months) Oakland, CA

Registered Nurse, PICU April 2015 - February 2019 (3 years 11 months)

Oakland, CA

Samuel Merritt University Adjunct Instructor May 2018 - Present (2 years 3 months)

San Francisco Bay Area

**ABSN** 

UCSF Medical Center Registered Nurse, PICU November 2014 - July 2016 (1 year 9 months)

San Francisco, CA

Kaiser Permanente Registered Nurse, PICU June 2014 - October 2014 (5 months) Oakland, CA

**Travel Nurse** 

Stanford Children's Health | Lucile Packard Children's Hospital Stanford
Registered Nurse, CVICU
March 2014 - June 2014 (4 months)
Palo Alto, CA

**Travel Nurse** 

Children's Hospital of Orange County (CHOC Children's)
Registered Nurse, CVICU
August 2013 - March 2014 (8 months)
Orange, CA

**Travel Nurse** 

University Hospitals
Registered Nurse, PICU
August 2011 - August 2013 (2 years 1 month)
Cleveland, OH

# Education

Kent State University
Bachelor of Science in Nursing (BSN), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2007 - 2011)